Sae byeol Pak

Front-end developer

(236) 986-2247

in linkedin.com/in/sae-pak

www.saepak.com

https://github.com/saepak

Profile

A detail-oriented front-end developer and self-motivated professional with extensive team collaboration involvement. Over three years experience building websites and web applications for a multitude of clients. Continually working on the improvement of technical skill levels through personal and team projects.

Technical Skills

SKILLS HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS / JavaScript / React.js / React Hooks / GraphQL / jQuery

TOOLS Visual Studio Code / Git / Android Studio / Xcode

OTHER UI framework / Trello / Slack / MS office

Project Experience

Easy Realty System / Front-end Developer

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

A property management system for professional real estate agents.

- Built the front-end of Easy Realty System's property lists and fetched API using React.js,
 React Hooks and Material-UI.
- Styled components with SASS for logical code organization.
- Tested all features for cross browser and multiple devices compatibility.

Kovan / Front-end Developer

May 2020 - Aug 2020

An all-in-one group management solution with 7 plug-ins.

- Collaborated with other students to plan and execute a native app.
- Built and implemented a to-do list and poll plug-in with React Native and React Hooks.
- Created graphs in poll plug-in with SVG for scalability and easy editing.
- Styled the app with Native-Base to reduce the built time.
- Made the promotional website using React.js. to show the seven different plug-ins and our marketing plans.

Personal Project Experience

Movie Box

A web app that lets you search for movies and TV shows.

- Created search and filter features using React.js.
- Fetched TMDB Movie API to provide massive data about movies and TV shows.
- Styled the components using Material-UI for responsive design.

Mini Memo

A simple note app that enables users to keep track of their tasks, ideas and goals.

- Built a server storing data using GraphQL to extend my knowledge to the back-end development.
- Used Apollo.js for easy management of the data.

Work Experience

Emeye (Seoul, South Korea) / UI developer

Dec 2015 - Dec 2017

- Built websites and web apps using HTML5, CSS3 and jQuery.
- Validated CSS style sheet using W3C Validation Service for error-free performances.
- Worked on websites maintenance including correcting issues and making updates to ensure that client's websites are running at full capacity.

Konest (Seoul, South Korea) / UI developer

Mar 2014 - May 2015

- Changed website code from HTML3 to HTML5 / CSS3 and made it responsive.
- Built web pages and updated the website for the up-to-date information delivery.
- Worked with clients to create customized landing pages for their marketing campaign.

Education

Langara college (Vancouver, Canada)

Post-Degree Diploma, Web and Mobile App Design and Development / Developer stream.

Sungshin Women's University (Seoul, South Korea)

Bachelor's degree, Japanese Language and Literature.





